Hello, hello friends, I have made a
video on how to understand insurance stock market.
I had explained this three years ago as
well. In my
video, I saw this
kind of hope in insurance market. Opportunities are there. It is
better than this. Sector-19 is
visible in the visibility because there is a
decade and a decade that indicates four digits like this,
which is a point. I can
see here that how will the insurance stock market be. The
shortcomings that are
visible today, okay, the leaders, okay, should
go behind the next four digit five. Till this year, they are saying that don't give any
surprises, okay, they will remain in some form or the other. Someone has become a
check, salary, I
can tell, but these shortcomings are going to be
so big in themselves that there is
no limit to them, I
mean, this is an amazing sector. Now,
why? And these three pins, which are the topic of today's
date, there is a
disclaimer in my portfolio. I have registered this also.  I
am not an advisor, okay, you can
buy any device and then the rest will be
fine, okay, I study for educational purposes
and I like to always study shares with the
people. Now these three stocks,
Jis Life is a potential Iis Law Board,
okay, the third company is Max, but
relatively I have two life insurances
and I don't think
I should keep the third stock, okay, it is life
insurance and the only one is Imphal Sil Ubal
which is listed in general insurance,
N8 Joint Giant,
so I am not going to talk much about these three companies,
okay,
I have written these three companies, shampoo, so that
you can see after two years, see after three years when the time will be
visible, okay and always compare shampoo
fees, okay in the time, okay, and what should I say with
all these stocks, they were
economical, okay, SG Silver had come till 330,
such circulation was shown till 240,
Lombard was shown at 90, okay, so
understand this point, Major Ali,
invest money only in these companies, PIMS  I had found
some banking stocks and was able to invest in Deep and Bloody
Mary. I do
n't have much money because I
invest a lot of money, but whatever
money I could invest, I invested in them. So, what I'm going to
talk to you about today is how to
understand these companies. So,
I'll tell you about some rescuers. This might seem a
little academic to you, but whenever
you're trying to understand
insurance and fuel, there are five major issues which you should try to
understand and data.
Okay, the dream is that the presidency persistence
members always digitize. Whenever the
final result of the deficiencies is declared,
it is also declared accordingly with them. Okay, this is
Idea's rule, so it's just a standstill,
that the customers who are old customers,
okay, how can they remove the policy? If
my premium is there, then I am paying my premium
next year as well, and then I will pay the next year as well.
So, this will be the persistence
itself. The calculator from Persistence E0 is also
given, which one can
use it.  How many seams of the famous defy that
such is the idea rule, okay, so this is something, the more the
persistence will be, I mean,
their customers are, this is a very strong belief in these
two products, insurance company, okay, it
happens that at today's date, in the exam, the
insurance company had to be closed, so what is this, set all your alarms that I, okay, the more serious any leader is, automatically the old investment becomes so disgusting, so actually its cost balance sheet, a back
insurance company commander, total
expense divided by we don't premium, so for example,
when I
clicked on whatever, explain why
setting achievement general insurance
company, so whatever is my balance,
whatever commission I paid in the search of the planet, I
spent some total morning
premium, assume that I got out of the job
and he paid up to 90% of the premium
- means the less it will be -
like Jyoti told here in Greater Noida
that I did Ravana and the 19th has passed, I got
₹10 at once  The problem is profit has been made
only blind premium wastage okay this is not the
only way for any insurance company to
count money suppose
this number this time commander Swiss one and
okay here birthday
thank you state quarter of saver mode no
profit no loss no nothing because the
money that gets clicked, the premium that you
pay now, then what does the premium do
that the companies make some unity director six
military unit Hindu 120 B Muktipath
semester so that is investment that
increases worry its value increases
and this is the biggest thing
of any insurance company as it increases
you feel what is happening means if there are many
comments like this
but this time it reaches in lakhs crores
subscribe
Kunjal these people mean don't be
surprised they have ₹1000000 such
investment so imagine that 10 lakh
crores even 15 percent then the
money of any insurance company comes
from the invested in settlement
how many settlements have you made  What was done and how much had come, to whom it was
handed over, in this your newly appointed, it
depends on the brand, it is okay that the
more you are setting it does not mean anything,
okay if it happens like this then it will be very important, the ghee will
reduce in its way, look into
your book, what are you doing, you
place your name, how much did you get and the
release of your premium, mostly the general
insurance companies started doing this number, in its Navodaya
class, how much did you get for your
premium, okay, let me
tell you from KC Day, how is the profitability
updating, okay now I will take you to
show some data,
we will see all the secrets, whenever we will
definitely give financial, okay now I will give you some
example of life which I will
show you here, okay now see these companies,
how their work is going on, in
2013, in this, developed screener,
total 14 in 2013, appointed in 2013, okay
this is a little bit, but right now the total is
not the total, you can brush it with this because
now cold also should come forward in protection,  Also recent
sister, one, this has also reached its peak, that is, the
company has grown three times
in how many years, okay, so next year
it will be 40 lakh 20 thousand crores, okay,
then next, 1968, see this in such a solid manner,
here no interest is given, the
speed does not decrease, okay, now
after that the net profit is 2440,
like sequence tortoise expenses,
generally explain claim is hot, the
rest of this, the mother with normal cost,
operating cost, those people are
equal, now see below,
about theirs, any money starts becoming
theirs, no money is about
them,
Rishi Janasi dedha, now this is taken, that is why image1 does
not stick to their receiver,
okay, okay, see, the
growth in this from the actress is very fast, it is
very fast, so now you see,
it will definitely remain in the order of 20 percent, 19 percent,
so it will keep increasing,
okay, team list of the house  Look at this cement, it has
come close to its lifetime high, so now if it
comes, it will not break brother, look at it,
how people are investing money, now I do
n't know if you missed it, see what you did,
but in this, look at f5, f5
was 8 percent in 2017, which is 23 percent today,
how much time more have you
invested just for exams, when the devices in serial life have
doubled from three to seven,
okay, your opinion is that it is lying between 7 to 8,
otherwise the promoters did not remove it,
fruits as much, let's talk first, recently I
logged in at 619, I sold it,
their stand, the company is still alive and
it did
not take even a second, everything gets sold, that's it, it is done for
you, similarly, if you take on the code number,
you will also see the loot, in the same way, there
is an info free reduction of 2017 Singhvi data,
so the premium Ratna for a Siddha here does
not have to be that much, but friends,
see the same premium, you can make more profit, Jut
General Insurance Company has floor him
Similar meaning Ismail Hussain in these,
but you will see the profit in them, here the
profit is increasing rapidly, the
premium that they pay is
one year's premium when they buy a car, at
this time the Khurram is over,
okay, so if you did not do anything with the insurance that you paid for Rs. 15000, then it
goes into your pocket in 15 days, okay,
for the third, the premium of the general insurance coming will be
small, that means the total renum will be
small, so that the profitability will
also be stronger than the typical life
insurance company, okay,
I just wanted to tell you today,
thank you very much and do
not forget to subscribe to the channel and keep tracking